{
    "id": "66c3bd5b00254027aeb6d9aad2b7bd92",
    "title": "Both, Either And Neither",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "I didn’t like ………………….. of these two dresses.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I like ………………….. of these. Have you got another one?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "………………….. of them have been invited.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "I have invited …………………. of them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "neither",
                "either"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "I haven’t invited ………………….. of them.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "They were ………………… eager to hear the news.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "either",
                "both",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… Martin and James are brilliant boys.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        },
        {
            "question": "‘I know you don’t like me. I don’t like you ……………….’",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "both",
                "either",
                "neither"
            ],
            "correct": 1
        },
        {
            "question": "………………… Martin nor James turned up today.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Both",
                "Either",
                "Neither"
            ],
            "correct": 2
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ………………….. intelligent nor hardworking.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "neither",
                "either",
                "both"
            ],
            "correct": 0
        }
    ]
}